Guide to the Rabbi Arthur Schneier Papers TAM.694
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I. Appeal of Conscience Foundation Material, 1964-2018, undated; 29 audiocassettes; 5 VHS; 52.75 Gigabytes in 6,985 computer files.; 32 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 59 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 2.5 small flat boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 2.5 media boxes.
  - Subseries I.C. Appeal of Conscience Foundation Delegations to Foreign Countries, 1966-2012, undated; 3 audiocassettes; 5 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and .25 media box.
    - 1981 ACF Delegation to China: Slides, 1981, undated; 2 folders (Box 250, Folder 24, Box 251, Folder 1)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Correspondence, Notes, and Schedules, 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 20)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Correspondence, Press, and Lists of Participants, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 229, Folder 12)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Correspondence and Travel Information -- Delegates, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Note and Photographs, 1981, undated; 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 14, 15)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Notes, Correspondence, and Lists of Delegates, 1979-1981, undated; 1 folder (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Press, Correspondence, List of Participants, and Schedule, 1980-1981, undated; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Report -- International Communication Agency, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Report, Itinerary, and Notes, 1981, undated; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Reports, Notes, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - 1981 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Hungary: Report and Photographs, 1981, undated; 1 folder (Box 229, Folder 15)
    - 1982 ACF Delegation to the Soviet Union: Hotel Information, Press, Reports, and Handouts, 1982-1983, undated; 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - 1982 ACF Delegation to the Soviet Union: Notes, Photographs, Correspondence, Travel Documents, and Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 15)
    - 1983 ACF Delegation to Bulgaria: Images and Correspondence, 1983, undated; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - 1983 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Correspondence, Press, Report Draft, and Photographs, 1983-1984, undated; 2 folders (Box 97, Folder 5, 6)
    - 1983 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs, Correspondence, and Brochures, 1983, undated; 2 folders (Box 97, Folder 3, 4)
    - 1983 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs and Negatives, 2 folders (Box 251, Folder 10, 11)
    - 1983 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs, Slide, Images, and Correspondence, 1983, undated; 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 26)
    - 1983 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Press, 2 folders (Box 257, Folder 11, 12)
    - 1983 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Report and Press, 1983, undated; 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 16)
    - 1983 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Slides, 2 folders (Box 251, Folder 2, 13)
    - 1985 ACF Delegation to the Soviet Union: Travel Documents, Correspondence, and Press, 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Brochures and Menus, 1986, undated; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Correspondence, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Correspondence, Notes, and Photographs, 1982-1986; 1 folder (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Guest Lists -- U.S. Ambassador's Luncheon for ACF, 1986, undated; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Notes, Correspondence, and Handout, 1986, undated; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Notes, Correspondence, Photographs and Itinerary, 1986, undated; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Photographs, 1986, undated; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Press, 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Reports, 1986, undated; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - 1986 ACF Delegation to China: Slides, 1986, undated; 2 folders (Box 251, Folder 3, Box 252, Folder 1)
    - 1988 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Press, Correspondence, Images, and Reports, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 231, Folder 21, Box 232, Folder 1)
    - 1988 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Press and Images, 1988, undated; 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - 1988 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Press, Lists of Delegates, Reports, Schedule, and Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 232, Folder 2-4)
    - 1989 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Travel Information, Correspondence, Itinerary, Press, and Reports, 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 20)
    - 1990 ACF Delegation to Hungary, Yugoslavia, and Romania: Booklets, Travel Information, and Correspondence, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - 1991 ACF Delegation to Albania: Photographs, Negatives, and Correspondence, 1991, undated; 2 folders (Box 122, Folder 16, Box 243, Folder 1)
    - 1992 ACF Delegation to Japan and China: Correspondence, Notes, Menus, Pictures, and Itineraries, 1 folder (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - 1992 ACF Delegation to Thailand: Contacts and Publication from the Thailand Office of the National Culture Commission, 1991, undated; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Correspondence, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 233, Folder 7, 8)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Requests for Information on China, 1991-1992; 3 folders (Box 232, Folder 13, Box 87, Folder 21, Box 233, Folder 12)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Correspondence and Booklets --Jewish-Chinese Affairs, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Correspondence and Lists of Contacts by Country, 1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Correspondence, Photographs, and Press, 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Invitations, Handouts, Notes -- American Consulate General Shanghai, 1991-1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Itineraries, Travel Information, Correspondence, and Report, 1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Menus, Brochures, Correspondence, and Memorabilia, 1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 232, Folder 14)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs -- Beijing, undated; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs -- The Great Wall, Bangkok, Hong Kong, and Beijing, 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs -- Old Synagogue in Shanghai, The Mayor, and U.S. Consulate Reception, 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs -- Rabbi Arthur Schneier Speaking at PES, 1994; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs -- with Sasakawa and Lord Kadoorie, undated; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs -- Xiamen and Hong Kong, 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs and Negatives -- Beijing, undated; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Photographs and Negatives -- Buddhist Abbott and RAS, Israel Ambassador to China in Beijing, and Mayor of Shanghai, undated; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Press and Notes, 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - 1992 ACF Interfaith Delegation to China: Reports, Notes, and Delegate Biographical Information, 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - 1992 ACF Romanian Conflict Resolution Training Program: Correspondence -- United States Department of State, 1986-1992; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - 1992 ACF Romanian Conflict Resolution Training Program: Grant Proposal -- United States Department of State, 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - 1993 ACF Delegation to Russia: Photographs and Negatives -- with Patriarch Aleksy II at Moscow, undated; 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 11)
    - 1993 ACF Delegation to Russia: Photographs -- with Rabbi Adolph Shayevitch, undated; 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 12)
    - 1993 ACF Delegation to Turkey: Photographs and Negatives, 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Booklets, 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 129, Folder 1, 2)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Release of Political Prisoners, 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Correspondence, Brochures, Name Tags, Notes, Press, and Speeches, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Correspondence and Press, 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Event Programs and Lists of Participants, 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Itinerary and Schedule -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur and Elizabeth Schneier, 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Photographs -- The International Seminar on Jews in Shanghai, 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 16)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Photographs, Negatives, and Correspondence, 1994, undated; 2 folders (Box 244, Folder 20, 21)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Photographs, Negatives, and Images, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 15)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Postcards, undated; 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 22)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Press, 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Speech with Notes by Rabbi Arthur Schneier, 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 13)
    - 1994 ACF Delegation to China: Speeches -- The International Seminar on Jews in Shanghai, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - 2000 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - 2000 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence, Itinerary, and Press, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - 2000 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Itinerary, Notes, and Contact Information, 2000, undated; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - 2000 ACF Delegation to Cuba: List of Delegates, and Travel Information, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - 2000 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Notes, Correspondence, and Itinerary, 3 folders (Box 232, Folder 9-11)
    - 2000 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Travel Information, Brochures, and Lists of Contacts, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - 2001 ACF Delegation to Romania: List of Delegates, Correspondence, Schedule, Photographs, and Press, 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - 2002 ACF Delegation to Russia and Armenia: Press, Agenda, Itinerary, and Correspondence, 2001-2002; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - 2002 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Armenia and Russia: Correspondence, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 22, Folder 1, 2)
    - 2002 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Armenia and Russia: Delegation List, Itinerary, and Schedules, 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - 2002 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Armenia and Russia: Media Advisory and List of News Organizations, 2001-2002; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - 2002 ACF Interfaith Delegation to Armenia and Russia: American Embassy Reception Guest List, 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - 2003 ACF Delegation to Hungary: Correspondence, Itinerary, and Press, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - 2003 ACF Delegation to Hungary: Schedule, Notes, Correspondence, and Press, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - 2006 ACF Delegation to Cuba to Celebrate the Centennial of the Jewish Community of Cuba: Correspondence, Lists of Guest Events, Schedules, and Itineraries, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - 2006 ACF Delegation to Cuba to Celebrate the Centennial of the Jewish Community of Cuba: Correspondence, Schedule, and Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - 2006 ACF Delegation to Cuba to Celebrate the Centennial of the Jewish Community of Cuba: Correspondence and Travel License -- Department of Treasury, 2005-2006, undated; 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - 2006 ACF Delegation to Cuba to Celebrate the Centennial of the Jewish Community of Cuba: Notes and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - 2006 ACF Delegation to Cuba to Celebrate the Centennial of the Jewish Community of Cuba: Press, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - 2006 ACF Delegation to Cuba to Celebrate the Centennial of the Jewish Community of Cuba: Programs, Contacts, and Brochure, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - 2006 ACF Delegation to Cuba to Celebrate the Centennial of the Jewish Community of Cuba: Travel Information, Itinerary, and Correspondence, 2006, undated; 1 folder (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - 2007 ACF Visit with Secretary-General of the United Nations: Press Releases, 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence -- Marazul Charters Inc., 1 folder (Box 237, Folder 4)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence -- Travel Information, 2008, undated; 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence, Schedule, and Event Guest Lists, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence and Travel License -- Department of Treasury, 1 folder (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Delegates' Biographical Information, Lists of Gifts Given to Hosts, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Flight and Hotel Information, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Images, 2008, undated; 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 27)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Press, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - 2008 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Schedules and Report Draft, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Biographical Information -- Delegates, 2012, undated; 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence -- Office of Foreign Assets Control, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence -- Travel Cellphone, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Correspondence -- Travel Information, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Itineraries, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Notes, 2012, undated; 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Notes -- Gifts for Cubans, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Press, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - 2012 ACF Delegation to Cuba: Schedule, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - ACF Delegation to Cuba: Sound Recordings, undated (Box 206, Cassette 694.0017, 694.0018, 694.0019)
    - ACF Delegation to Georgia and Soviet Union: Press and Flyer, undated; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Subseries I.D. International Political and Religious Leaders Hosted by Appeal of Conscience Foundation, 1968-2014, undated; 3 audiocassettes; 2.01 Gigabytes in 973 computer files.; 6.5 Linear Feet in 11.5 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, .5 small flat box, and 1 media box.
    This subseries contains audio cassette tapes, sound and video recordings, correspondence, images, photographs, newspaper clippings, photographs, schedules, and reports pertaining to the international political and religious leaders that meet with, or were hosted by the Appeal of Conscience Foundation during their visit to the United States. Delegations came from the following countries: Bosnia and Herzegovina, China, Serbia, Yugoslavia, Russia, Romania, and Hungary. Well known religious and political leaders hosted by the Foundation include: Romanian Chief Rabbi Moses Rosen, Rabbi Levin, Ukrainian President Leonid Kravchuk, Russian Orthodox Patriarch Aleksy II, French President Nicolas Sarkozy, and Chinese Ambassador Li Dayou. There are some born-digital media--images, sound and video recordings--in this subseries.
    This subseries is grouped chronologically by year of event, then arranged alphabetically by type.
    - 1968 ACF Reception in Honor of Rabbi Levin: Correspondence and Press, 1 folder (Box 248, Folder 30)
    - 1968 ACF Reception in Honor of Rabbi Levin: Correspondence, Press, and Notes, 1 folder (Box 248, Folder 31)
    - 1968 ACF Reception in Honor of Rabbi Levin: Photographs and Film, 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - 1972 ACF Reception in Honor of Chief Rabbi Moses Rosen's 60th Birthday: Photograph, Press, Lists of Attendees, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - 1972 ACF Reception in Honor of Chief Rabbi Moses Rosen's 60th Birthday: Press and Speech, 1 folder (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - 1974 ACF Reception for Dr. Seifert: Correspondence and Press, 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - 1974 ACF Reception for Rabbi Moses Rosen: Correspondence, Photographs, Notes, and List of Guests, 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - 1975 ACF Reception for Soviet Union Religious Leaders Delegation: Correspondence, Guest Lists, Notes, and Press, 2 folders (Box 193, Folder 12, 13)
    - 1975 ACF Reception for Soviet Union Religious Leaders Delegation: List of Delegates and Interpreters, 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - 1976 ACF Luncheon in Honor of the Empress of Iran: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 227, Folder 7, 8, Box 193, Folder 5)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Correspondence -- Donation Requests, 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 13)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Correspondence and Press, 1976, undated; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 12, Box 227, Folder 11)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Itineraries, Correspondence, Expenses, and Press, 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Itinerary, undated; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 20)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Notes -- On Protocol, 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Notes and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Photographs, 1976, undated; 8 folders (Box 238, Folder 20, Box 113, Folder 1-6, Box 193, Folder 3)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Press, 7 folders (Box 76, Folder 13, Box 77, Folder 9, Box 238, Folder 21, 26, Box 193, Folder 4, 10, 11)
    - 1976 ACF Meeting with Inter-religious Soviet Union Delegation: Press and Notes, 2 folders (Box 227, Folder 9, 10)
    - 1978 ACF Hosts Dinner in Honor of Patriarch Maxim of Bulgaria: Photographs, Photographic Contact Sheets, and Press, 1978, undated; 1 folder (Box 242, Folder 13)
    - 1978 ACF Luncheon for Assistant Secretary of State: Correspondence, Press, and Notes, 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Biographical Information, Lists of Participants, and Correspondence, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Correspondence, 1979-1980; 3 folders (Box 79, Folder 6, 13, Box 259, Folder 17)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Correspondence -- International Communications Agency, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Correspondence, Notes, and Hotel Information, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 19)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Negatives, 1 folder (Box 249, Folder 9)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Notes, Lists of Delegate Names, and Correspondence, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Press, Correspondence, and Reports, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Press, Lists of Delegates, and Schedule, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Press, Photographs, and Visit Information, 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Report Drafts, Notes, and Luncheon Table Seating Information, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Schedule, 1 folder (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts First Interfaith Delegation of Religious Leaders from Hungary: Schedule and Photographs, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 230, Folder 22, 23, Box 231, Folder 1)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Correspondence and Lists of Invitees, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Correspondence, Notes, Itinerary, and Reports, 1979-1980, undated; 2 folders (Box 231, Folder 5, 6)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Invitations and Press, 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Itineraries, 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 18)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Negatives, 1 folder (Box 249, Folder 10)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Photo Album, 1 folder (Box 116)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Press, 1979, undated; 4 folders (Box 230, Folder 17, Box 231, Folder 3, Box 208, Folder 24, Box 34, Folder 6)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Press and Schedule, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 242, Folder 19)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Reports, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 21)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Reports, Notes, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - 1979 ACF Hosts Romanian Interfaith Delegation: Sound Recording and Press, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 16, Box 206, Cassette 694.0016)
    - 1979 ACF Luncheon in Honor of Interfaith Delegation from Romania: Correspondence -- Invitations, 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - 1979 ACF Luncheon in Honor of Interfaith Delegation from Romania: Lists of Participants, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 14)
    - 1979 ACF Luncheon in Honor of Interfaith Delegation from Romania: Program and Guest List, 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - 1980 ACF Reception in Honor of Ryoichi Sasakawa: Citation, Photographs, and Photographic Contact Sheets, 1980, undated; 1 folder (Box 242, Folder 17)
    - 1980 ACF Reception in Honor of Ryoichi Sasakawa: Correspondence, Notes, and Press, 1 folder (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - 1982 ACF Reception in Honor of the Russian Orthodox Church Delegation: Correspondence -- Pimen, Patriarch, 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - 1983 ACF Hosts the Romanian Minister of Religious Affairs, Ion Rosianu: Correspondence, Notes, and Press, 2 folders (Box 80, Folder 15, 16)